TZE FUNG JIM LUNG

1067, 59th Street, Brooklyn, NY 11219

Tel: (917) 214 – 0908 | fung10_91@hotmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/tze-fung-lung-0a9111164/

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Bilingual master graduate in data science with Intern experience in data analysis seeking a challenging position in the data analysis and engineering field where relevant expertise can be utilized

SKILLS

Excellent working knowledge of R and Python for financial analysis and Data Science skills. Other areas of expertise include data scraping, data cleaning and imputation, data visualization, data mining and modeling, machine learning, Hadoop, Mathematics and statistics programming. BI analysis tool – Mode. Foreign language: Cantonese and Mandarin

Work Sample: https://fung1091.shinyapps.io/profile/

EDUCATION

Master's Degree of Data Science at City University of New York (CUNY) (April 2019, GPA: 3.9)

BEng in Manufacturing Informatics and Systems Engineering from City University of Hong Kong

Bachelor of Health Science from RMIT University

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Data Analyst - Various clients

May. 2019 - Now

 Provided complex and intensive data analysis related to data scraping, visualization, mining, and Excel formation and Pivot table

Intern - Kasisto, New York, NY

Jan. 2019 – Apr. 2019

- Improved and extracted the data sourcing pipeline and the natural language in chat-bot
- Developed and supported of a wide range of data transformations and migrations
- Constructed custom ETL processes

Co-Founder - Newinsock.com, New York, NY

Jan. 2017 – Dec. 2018

- Conducted sourcing for products to ensure constant and timely supply of inventory; coordinated shipping and professional packaging for product orders; provided detailed follow-through and after sales service for customer satisfaction
- Designed comprehensive web pages for business using Wordpress and SEO setting

Safety Officer - PCCW Solutions, Hong Kong

Dec. 2015 – Dec. 2016

- Organized details and workflow of a safety and health training program
- Conducted monthly safety committee meetings to discuss and monitor progress
- Performed daily inspection for various parts of the project and recorded all documentations and procedures involved
- Prepared detailed training records, inspection reports, inspection photos, drill reports and accident records

Safety Officer – Hsin Chong Construction Co. LTD, Hong Kong

Sep. 2012 – Aug. 2015

- Played an integral part of the construction project of subway stations and tunnels
- Provided professional consultation and safety advice, Conducted regular safety inspection and reported for findings

QUALIFICATIONS AND CREDENTIALS

Real Estate License (Jan. 2018); Graduate Member – Institution of Occupational Safety and Health (2014)